Guide to the Silliman College, Yale University, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Silliman College, Yale University, records of the dean
1978-1994
RU 804
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2.5
(3 boxes)
The records consist of freshmen and commencement files maintained by the dean of Silliman College, Yale University.
Silliman College (Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 13-L-1 (YRG 13-L-1), Records of the dean of Silliman College.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of freshmen and commencement files maintained by the dean of Silliman College, Yale University.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
College students; Student housing; Universities and colleges -- Administration; Silliman College (Yale University); Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Student housing; Yale University -- Students
- Freshman and commencement records for the Classes of 1981-1984, 1977-1984; Accession 1993-A-075
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2060.
  - Commencement
    - Class of 1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Class of 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Class of 1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Class of 1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Freshmen Folder
    - Class of 1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Class of 1982 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Class of 1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Class of 1984 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Freshman and commencement records for the Classes of 1985-1987, 1981-1987; Accession 1994-A-031
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2063.
  - Class of 1985 Freshman Folder Freshman Counselors, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1985 Freshman Folder Freshman Faculty Advisors, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1985 Freshman Folder General (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1985 Commencement (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
  - Class of 1986 Freshman Folder Freshman Faculty Advisors (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1986 Freshman Folder General and Freshman Counselors (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1986 Commencement (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
  - Class of 1987 Freshman Folder Freshman Counselors (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Class of 1987 Freshman Folder Faculty Advisors (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Class of 1987 Freshman Folder: General (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Class of 1987 commencement (Box 2, Folder 13-14)
- Freshman and commencement records for the Classes of 1993-1994, 1989-1994; Accession 2001-A-091
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2070.
  - Commencement 1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Commencement 1993, Silliman (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1994, 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Freshman counsellor applications, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Freshman faculty advisers, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)